EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

A software development and performance engineering with 3 years of experience in the high-tech manufacturing and Internet industries. Strong analytical abilities, questioning mind and critical thinking, fast learner - quickly fits in, team player with great interpersonal skills, experienced in managing, comfortable at teaching & publicly speaking, very passionate about front-end developing.

Please Note: After a few years developing Drivers (linux), now applying for FRONT-END/FULL-STACK position. For more information please refer to my page: https://tomshaffir.github.io/tom-portfolio/

EDUCATION

2017-2018 Certificate: Angular 2+, JavaScript from Coursera.

2012-2016 B.sc. in COMPUTER SCIENCE; Tel Hai College. (GPA score: 85). Psychometric score: 720.

2003-2006 Full matriculation; Math, Physics, English (5 Units), emek High School (score: 106)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PRESENT - FRONT END PROFESSIONAL COURSES

Deeply learning & Hands-on Projects building on the following topics:

♦ CSS 3
♦ JAVASCRIPT
♦ ES5/ES6
♦ REDUX (BASIC)
♦ TYPESCRIPT
♦ ANGULAR 2+

❖ ANGULAR STYLING & ANIMATIONS
❖ BOOTSTRAP
❖ HTML 5

2015-2017 MELLANOX TECHNOLOGIES. LINUX DRIVERS DEVELOPER

Mellanox Technologies is an Israeli supplier of end-to-end InfiniBand and Ethernet interconnect solutions.

- R&D team, Researching & Developing complex data traffic abilities (Ethernet, Infiniband).
- Drivers coding (Infiniband) on both C & Assembly.
- Code testing via Python scripts writing.
- Using Scrum work method as a company standard.

2014-2015 ELBIT SYSTEMS, RT EMBEDDED (STUDENT JOB)

international technology company engaged in a wide range of defense, security and commercial programs.

A student job assigned to RT embedded team. Writing C code for Video improvement and stability.

2013 COMPUTER SCIENCE PREPARATORY, TEL - HAI COLLEGE, TEACHER ASSISTANT

The College promotes and emphasizes the advancement of science, society and the environment in Israel.

- Teaching introduction to computer science, 5 level mathematics and Assembly.
- Frontal teaching both groups & individuals.

MILITARY SERVICE

2006-2011 RANK: Officer captain (3 stripes). Permanent service as intelligence officer in Unit 76/8200.

TECHNOLOGIES & CODING

C, Assembly, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, Firebase, Git, TCP/IP, OSPF, STP, IGMP, VRRP and more

LANGUAGES

Hebrew - Primary Language | English - High Level